{
    "id": "f02c799ae9d34eaf8085034e53c9b316",
    "title": "Few, Little, A Few, A Little",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "7dc2e0c42a1549b88245994b07da57d1",
            "title": "Few vs. Little",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He was not a popular guy. He had very ........................... friends.",
                    "description": "Few means almost none. It can be used with very.",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "a few",
                        "little"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have met him only ........................... times.",
                    "description": "A few indicates a small number.",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "a few",
                        "little"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We have ............................. money. We can't eat out tonight.",
                    "description": "Little means almost nothing.",
                    "answers": [
                        "little",
                        "a little",
                        "a few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "There are ............................ apples in the fridge if you are hungry.",
                    "description": "A few indicates a small number.",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "a few",
                        "little"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "There was ............................. oil in the tank. It was almost empty.",
                    "description": "Little oil means almost no oil.",
                    "answers": [
                        "little",
                        "a little",
                        "few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has .......................... patience.",
                    "description": "Little patience means almost no patience.",
                    "answers": [
                        "little",
                        "a little",
                        "a few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have got ............................ money so you can buy that shirt if you want.",
                    "description": "A little indicates a small amount.",
                    "answers": [
                        "little",
                        "a little",
                        "a few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Only ................................ politicians are honest.",
                    "description": "Only a few means the same as few.",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "a few",
                        "the few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ate ................................ food and then went to bed.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "a few",
                        "a little",
                        "few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I got only .............................. answers correct.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "a few",
                        "a little"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": ".......................... people can afford a cruise holiday. It is very expensive.",
                    "description": "Only a few means the same as few.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Few",
                        "A little",
                        "Only a few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "There are very ............................... people that I really respect.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "a few",
                        "little"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}